[](https://www.pacificlife.com/home.html) _search_

* Products _keyboard\_arrow\_down_
    
    _keyboard\_arrow\_left_back
    
    _close_
    
    * [Annuities](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/products/annuities.html "Annuities") Pacific Life offers a variety of annuities designed to help grow, protect, and manage retirement savings turning it into steady, reliable lifetime income based on your personal preferences and goals.
    * [Life Insurance](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/products/life-insurance.html "Life Insurance") Life insurance is most commonly used to help protect your family from any financial effects of your and/or your spouse's death. Protect your family's financial well-being with life insurance, which can pay a death benefit to help replace a lifetime of your loved one's lost earning potential.
    * [For Institutions](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/products/institutions.html "For Institutions") Whether you’re looking for a de-risking strategy for your company’s pension plan, want to provide financial security to your retirees, or looking for a strong investing partner, Pacific Life has the solutions and experience to help you succeed.
    * [Workforce Benefits](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/products/workforce-benefits.html "Workforce Benefits") Pacific Life is revolutionizing employee benefits by empowering you with a premier, comprehensive, friction-free, digitally native experience.
    
* About Us _keyboard\_arrow\_down_
    
    _keyboard\_arrow\_left_back
    
    _close_
    
    * [About Us](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/about.html "About Us") Whether you’re protecting your loved ones or growing your assets, you’re highly invested in your financial future. And so are we. When you purchase life and retirement insurance, you’re buying a promise. A promise that today, tomorrow or ten years from now, we’ll be there. For nearly 160 years, we’ve fulfilled that promise. Our clients trust Pacific Life to protect what matters most to them—their families, their businesses, their futures.
    
* _search_

_account\_circle_Login _keyboard\_arrow\_right_

_keyboard\_arrow\_left_BACK

_menu_More

_keyboard\_arrow\_right_

_close_Close

###### [For Financial Professionals](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/benefits-of-working-with-us.html)

###### [Careers](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/Careers.html)

###### [Investor Relations](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/investor-relations.html)

###### [Contact Us](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/contact-us.html)

SEARCH _close_

_search_

_clear_

SEARCH

[Home](https://www.pacificlife.com/home.html) / [Privacy & Other Policies](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies.html) /

* [Online Privacy Policy _keyboard\_arrow\_down_](#) [Legal Information & Website Usage](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/legal-information-and-website-usage.html) [New York Confidentiality for Domestic Violence Victims and Endangered Individuals](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/new-york-confidentiality-for-domestic-violence-victims-and-endan.html) [Our Privacy Promise](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/our-privacy-promise.html) [Help Us Protect Your Privacy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/help-us-protect-your-privacy.html) [Social Media Guidelines](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/social-media-guidelines.html) [Online Privacy Policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/online-privacy-policy.html) [Your Personal Information](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/your-personal-information.html) [Global Procurement Solutions](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/enterprise-procurement.html) [Human Rights Policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/human-rights-policy.html) [ACA Transparency in Coverage Provisions](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/aca-transparency-in-coverage-provisions.html) [Environmental Policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/environmental-policy.html) [Responsible Product Offerings](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/responsible-product-offerings-policy.html) [Climate Risk Disclosure and Report](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/climate-risk-disclosure-and-report.html) [HIPAA Notice of Privacy Practices](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/hipaa-notice-of-privacy-practices.html) [United States Employee/Contractor Privacy Policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/united-states-employee-and-contractor-privacy-policy.html) [Occupational Health and Safety Policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/occupational-health-and-safety-policy.html) [Responsible Marketing Policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/responsible-marketing-policy.html) [Instructions for Serving Pacific Life](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/instructions-for-serving-pacific-life.html)

Online Privacy Policy
---------------------

**Introduction  
**The privacy of your information is important to us. We are committed to maintaining the highest level of confidentiality with all of the information we receive through our websites.

Pacific Life has established the following Online Privacy Policy that describes how we use the information we collect from our website visitors. To learn more about how we protect information that is collected when you apply for a product or service, please refer to [Our Privacy Promise](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/our-privacy-promise.html).

**Collection and Use of Personal Information  
**Visitors are not required to provide personal information to browse the information found on our websites. Personal information is only collected when you voluntarily provide it to us, for example when you first log into your account or submit personal information in an online form. Personal information may include first and last name, address, email address, telephone number, and Social Security number.

Information provided by you through our websites is used only to help maintain the business relationship you have with us, or encourage such a relationship. We do not sell information about you. We do not share your information with anyone else for their marketing purposes.

**Tracking Website Visitors  
**Pacific Life gathers aggregate tracking information from our website visitors. This aggregate tracking information is:

1. Collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no personal information is associated with this data.
2. Gathered through the use of Web server logs and cookies. A Web server log is a file where website activity is stored. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website sends to a visitor's computer, which is stored on his or her hard drive. Pacific Life uses cookies to track repeat visits to its website. Although Pacific Life assigns a cookie to a visitor's computer, the company does not know who that visitor is unless that person specifically tells us.
3. Shared among Pacific Life business units to improve website content and overall service.
4. Used for purposes of direct marketing to visitors to our website through social platforms.

To enable us to continually improve the content we offer our website visitors, as well as for systems administration purposes, we collect aggregate information site-wide. This gives us an idea of which parts of our website you are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means a visitor's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous.

_If Pacific Life receives 'do not track' signals, we do not take any action to comply with such requests._

**Website Security  
**Pacific Life is committed to protecting the personal information you entrust to us. That is why we use the most current encryption technology available to ensure secure transmission of your information provided through our secure log in screens and online forms.

Please understand that the Internet is not a completely secure medium of communication. Unless the specific access location says otherwise, messages sent to or from this website may be accessed by unauthorized users. To protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information that you want kept confidential.

If you are concerned about the security of the Internet for the communication of personal information, you may consider using alternative forms of communication such as telephone, fax, or regular mail.

We do not guarantee or warrant that any part of this Website, including files available for download, are free of viruses or other harmful code. It is your responsibility to take appropriate precautions, such as the use of anti-virus software, to protect your computer hardware and software while using the Internet.

**Please review this Online Privacy Policy frequently as it may change at any time at Pacific Life's sole discretion.**

Last reviewed: 12/5/2022

Client Account Sign-In

Financial Professionals Sign-In

Products & Solutions

About Us

Menu

Copyright © Pacific Life Insurance Company [Privacy & Other Policies](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies.html)  

This website or its third-party tools use cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and are required to achieve the purposes illustrated in our [online privacy policy](https://www.pacificlife.com/home/privacy-and-other-policies/online-privacy-policy.html).

Accept & Close
